espc.com 2005-03-08

# ESPC Homeline

Introduction

ESPC (UK) Ltd respects your privacy and shall at all times comply with the Data Protection Act 1998.

When you register for ESPC (UK) Ltd's Homeline services, ESPC (UK) Ltd will store your personal data on its database, which is used by ESPC (UK) Ltd (and authorised third parties on behalf of ESPC (UK) Ltd) for client administration and marketing purposes.

Collecting personal information

We may, from time to time, send you mailings by e-mail, SMS or contact you by telephone in relation to products and/or services which you have requested or we feel may interest you and/or are relevant to you. The information we may send to you, or contact you about may include:-

  * details of houses for sale or rent;
  * details of our products and services, or events relating to our products or services;
  * newsletters;Informing you of any service-related changes which may affect your use of Homeline, or to let you know about any new features or functionality (e.g. the introduction of a new e-mail or chat service).
  * enquiring as to whether you would like to attend a research group to help us improve our service.

Passing details to other companies  
f you opt to receive information from other companies, we may sometimes disclose your personal details to those companies in question. We will only do so, however, where those companies have undertaken not to use your personal information for any purpose other than to provide you with information. If you decide that you no longer wish to receive information from a particular company, you should contact that company directly. Please note that any subsequent personal information given to another company will be used according to that company's privacy policy; the ESPC (UK) policy will no longer apply.

Third party sites  
Our privacy policy does not apply to third party sites that you may access from ESPC (UK) Ltd's website. You should ensure, therefore, that you are familiar with the applicable privacy policy or other applicable terms and conditions before entering any personal information on a third party site.

Updating and amending your personal information  
As a registered customer, you have control over the accuracy of your personal information. If, at any time, you wish to verify, update or amend the personal information you have given to Homeline, you can do so on-line by clicking on "Update my Details" on your personal Homeline home page. If you would like to see the information ESPC (UK) Ltd holds about you or would like to be removed from any of our mailing lists, please write to our data protection officer at the address below.

To help us keep our database up-to-date, we would be grateful if you would let us know as soon as any of your contact details change or if you notice any inaccuracies in them.

Changes to Privacy Policy  
First and foremost, we recognise the importance of privacy to our customers and visitors, and intend to remain at the cutting edge of industry developments in this area. We will keep this policy under review, and any changes made from time to time will be posted on this page.

Consent  
By disclosing your personal information to us, or by continuing as a customer if you have already registered, you indicate your consent to the collection, storage, processing and use of your personal information by ESPC (UK) Ltd as described in this privacy policy.

Data Protection Officer  
ESPC (UK) Ltd  
90A George Street  
Edinburgh  
Midlothian  
EH2 3DF
